All right, all bets are in.
Rupert, bad idea trusting the Celtics.
Worse than when I trusted Brian
to pack my parachute.
Hey, Brian, care to place a wager?
Tomorrow night on Fox's Celebrity Boxing,
I've got Carol Channing beating
Mike Tyson in three rounds.
Carol Channing.
You've got Carol Channing, the actress,
beating Mike Tyson, the boxer.
- Hell, give me $50 on Tyson.
- Well, you're in good company.
Betting Freddy took the same wager.
Bet!
Wait a minute.
There's nothing funny about an addiction.
Vote no on Indian gaming laws.
And we're back with
Fox Celebrity Boxing
with Mike Tyson and Carol Channing.
I tell you, Jim, how Carol Channing
outlasted that barrage
in the second round, we'll never know.
Come here, young man.
I'm gonna bop you one.
- She's getting beat!
- No, she's getting mad.
You ain't so tough, young man.
That all you got, you son of a bitch?
You're going down, young man.
You're going down!
I can't believe this. She keeps getting up.
I'm so exhausted.
And the winner, by technical knockout,
weighing in at 67 pounds,
Carol "Put On Your Sunday Clothes"
Channing.
Yeah.
Up yours, young people.
You and your rock and roll 8-track tapes!
I don't believe this. I just lost a $50 bet.
You know,
Mike Tyson once beat up his wife.
But there's nothing funny about that.
- Hi, guys. We're back from the mall.
- I got new shoes.
The old ones are in the box.
They smell and are old.
Hey, Peter, your 25th high-school reunion
is next Sunday.
Throw that away. I don't want to go.
Besides, Sunday's my Internet porn night.
Oh, yeah!
You're my Chinese Lois.
Hey, it's me. Knock, knock.
- So, you got my money?
- Oh, yeah. I'll pay you soon.
Yeah, well, here's a suggestion.
Have the money by tomorrow,
and there won't be any problems.
- Huh?
- Yeah, 24 hours.
Why? What happens in 24 hours?
I don't know. I'm not psychic, man.
I'm just saying it would probably be
better for everybody
- if you had the money tomorrow.
- Yeah, all right.
- I'll see what I can do.
- Sweet, sweet. Great.
- How's everything else going?
- Good.
All right. All right, see you later.
Don't forget.
No, you're not gonna forget.
Hey, Peter, I was going through
your garbage,
and I noticed your high-school
reunion is coming up.
Why were you going through my garbage?
Well, when I stopped over earlier,
I noticed Lois clipping her toenails,
and I thought,
"Oh, man, I got to get in on that. "
Huh.
Yeah, I don't think
I'm going to my reunion.
Everybody's all got their nice cars,
and their big, important jobs,
and their fancy hats,
and their fresh strawberries
so big you can eat them like a hand fruit.
Peter, everyone lies at those things.
Just tell them you're a big shot.
Wait a second, Joe, that's a great idea.
Boy, imagine what it would be like
to be a big shot.
Diego? Sweaty.
Thank you.
- Stewie, hey.
- Hey, there. So, it's been 24 hours.
- Got my money?
- You know what?
Just give me till next Friday.
I'll have it for you.
That's funny.
I could have sworn I said have it today.
- Yeah, I don't have it, sorry.
- Well. All right, then.
That's good OJ.
- Yeah, that hurt? That hurt?
- What the hell?
Yeah, doesn't feel so good, does it? No?
- Yeah, that's what happens, man.
- Oh, my God.
Yeah, that's what happens.
Where's my money?
You gonna give me my money?
Where's my money, man?
Where's the money?
Yeah, you like that? That feel good?
That feel good?
Where's the money, man?
Where's my money?
You've got till 5:00. You hear me?
You got till 5:00.
- You freaking psychopath!
- Clean yourself up.
Peter, this is ridiculous.
Why can't you just be yourself?
Lois, just go along with it.
Act like I'm a big shot.
- Hey, Peter Griffin, is that you?
- Hey, Mike, long time no see.
Wow. What...
- What's all this?
- This? I just came from work.
- I'm a secret agent astronaut millionaire.
- Cool. Where'd you get the cowboy hat?
- Space.
- By the way, this is my friend, Tom.
You're Tom Brady
from the New England Patriots!
Oh, man, I got to tell you,
you kick ass, man.
In fact, I was just saying
that the other day
to all the guys down at the brewery.
Brewery? I thought you were
a cowboy astronaut millionaire.
He's a fake!
Look, this cowboy hat comes right off.
Coming here was a huge mistake, Lois.
Peter, I know you're humiliated,
but getting drunk is not the answer.
Uh-oh. Either my esophagus just
got shorter, or I'm about to throw up.
Peter, that was amazing.
I've never seen a guy your size
who could move like that.
How would you like to play
for the New England Patriots?
I'd love to.
Say, listen, Tom,
could you get me a towel?
I threw up on the floor.
Sure.
And could you also get another towel?
I also threw up
on this gentleman's bare lap.
Could you wet the towel?
- Wet the towel, Tom?
For our top story tonight,
we go live to terrific haircut Bob Costas
as he talks with local man Peter Griffin,
who is living his dream of playing
for the New England Patriots.
- Bob?
- Thanks, Tom.
I'm fond of your hair, as well.
I'm standing here with Tom Brady
and his newest teammate, Peter Griffin.
Hey, Ma! Check it out!
I'm married to a pro athlete!
What do you think of that?
We're really excited to have Peter.
I think he's gonna make a great addition
to a great team.
I want to thank God.
I want to thank the Lord God.
'Cause it's not really up to me.
It's up to him.
And I want to thank the devil, too.
You know, 'cause that's why God's there.
He's minding the fence,
making sure that guy never comes back.
Uh...
You know, if it weren't for the devil,
God'd probably go insane,
blow his brains out from boredom,
you know?
Everybody likes to feel useful.
Maketh the world go round.
Back to you, Tom.
Diane, didn't your first husband
blow his brains out?
Oh, God.
Coming up, America's hottest new
curse word, "kleeman. "
We'll tell you what it means after this.
Boy, Lois, I can't believe
this is happening to me.
I'm somebody now, you know?
I don't have to lie to people
about my life anymore.
Oh, I am so happy for you, Peter.
What the hell happened to you?
I fell down the stairs.
Oh, you should be more careful.
All right, I'm ready. Come on, good game.
Good game, everybody. Yeah.
Come on, good game.
Let's get out there. Let's do it. Yeah, yeah.
110%, everybody. 110%.
Come on, let's go. Let's go. Good game!
Ready! Blue 20, blue 20! Hut, hut!
- Griffin, let go!
- Let's go?
- Morning.
- Good day to you, sir.
Hey, wait a minute. What the hell?
Getting real tired of you ducking me,
man. Yeah?
- Oh, my God!
- Yeah, getting really tired.
Where's my money? Where's my money?
Yeah, you got money to pay
for fake mustaches, huh? Yeah.
Yeah, how much you pay
for that fake mustache?
$2.99.
Listen, you just got to give me
more time...
Don't make a fool out of me, man.
Don't make a fool out of me.
I want my money.
I want my money, man.
Stewie, listen, this is crazy. You got...
Oh, my God.
All right, let's go to the bank.
Well, I got to tell you,
this was a delicious dinner, Mrs. Griffin.
- Well, the pleasure is all ours, Mr. Brady.
- Please, call me Tom.
- Can I call you Tom, too?
- Well, of course.
Mr. Brady, would you please sign
my Trapper Keeper?
Oh, Tom, your shirt. I'm so sorry.
- Look, you can use our shower if you want.
- No, it's okay.
It's just a little spot. It'll come out.
Well, that's not gonna come out.
You better take a shower.
- Mom, let me look!
- Meg, stop shoving.
You wouldn't even know
what to do with it.
He's closer to my age, you cow.
- What the hell is this?
- Oh, hi, Stewie.
- We were just leaving.
- I say, what the devil is all the fuss about?
I don't get it. What's in there?
Bing, bong! Hello!
- Hey. What's going on?
- What the hell? Get out of here!
What? We're on the same team.
We shower together.
- Yeah, in the locker room.
- Yeah, yeah, come here, you.
Stop it. Knock it off. What, are you crazy?
We're just a couple of guys
messing around.
That's what we are.
Quiet, everybody, my commercial's on.
Hi, I'm Peter Griffin
of the New England Patriots.
I'm here to kick off the Touchdown
of Savings weekend
at Wilkins Hyundai and Subaru.
We will blitz the competition,
and in no time,
you'll be driving your new Hyundai
or Subaru right to a touchdown.
Mom, the game's about to start.
Where's Dad?
I don't know, Chris.
And I'm starting to get worried.
I think all this success
might be going to his head.
Do you know he spent
$30,000 on a wax sculpture
of Harriet Tubman
doing Gwyneth Paltrow?
Yeah. Yeah,
that is happening for real. Yeah.
Yeah.
I'll enjoy that more tomorrow.
Where the hell is Griffin?
It's almost time for kickoff.
Well, I guess we have
to start without him.
What do you think?
I got this for doing that car dealership ad.
All right, enough messing around.
Let's play this game.
Let's play some football.
Griffin, I'm getting really tired
of your cocky attitude.
How many times have I told you,
no showboating?
Relax, Tom, I'm just having a little fun.
I got it under control.
Okay, 28-Z right, pitch left, on one, on one.
Ready? Break!
Ready, green 54! Green 54! Set, hut, hut!
Yeah!
There might be some hope
for this guy after all.
Yeah.
Damn it, Griffin! I said no showboating!
This calls for a victory tune!
No! No!
All right. I made a touchdown.
- Griffin, you're fired!
- For what?
We've had it with your crap.
I talked to the coach, and
he's selling your contract to another team.
And the only one that'll take you
is the worst football team in Europe,
the London Silly Nannies.
So, Brian, we're even now, right?
Ready to start a new life in England.
I've got my money.
Your wounds have healed up nicely.
What do you say
we let bygones be bygones?
You shot me in both my knees,
then lit me on fire. Piss off.
All right, all right. I tell you what,
- you get one free revenge shot at me.
- Okay.
But I'm not gonna tell you
when it's coming.
This is gonna be fun.
Peter, this is crazy.
Isn't there any way the Patriots
could let you back on the team?
No, they said the decision was final.
It's all right, Lois.
I can make the best of this.
I mean, a British football team
can't be that bad.
Excuse me. Hey, there.
Hi. I'm Peter Griffin. I'm your new player.
Oh, yes, Peter.
Welcome to the Silly Nannies.
I'm the quarterback, Lesley.
This is our team.
Oh, crap.
I guess living in a London flat
isn't gonna be too bad, huh?
- Mom, there's no water in the toilet.
- First of all, Chris, it's called a loo.
Second, there's no water in it,
because everybody here
just uses Elizabeth Hurley.
All right, well, where is she?
'Cause I need her now!
You're watching BBC FOUR.
Previously on Condensation.
Ellen, there's moisture
on the outside of my glass.
- It's condensation, Johnny.
- But what about the fog on the windows?
It's not fog, Johnny.
It, too, is called condensation.
'"Con-den-sation. '"
Hey, Peter, how was your first
Silly Nannies practice?
It sucked, Lois.
Those Silly Nannies
are just a bunch of losers.
- Pack your bags. We're going home.
- What, you're just giving up?
Look, Peter, I know you're upset
because you blew your opportunity
with the Patriots.
But this is your chance to redeem yourself.
Now, I bet if you really tried,
you could turn that team around.
You know what, Lois?
When you were talking about that sale
at TJ Maxx just now,
I came up with an idea.
I am going to turn that team around.
And we'll challenge the Patriots to a game,
and we'll kick their ass!
Oh, man, what an attractive woman.
- Hello?
- Hey, Brady, you're dead!
Listen, Leno, you keep calling here
and threatening me,
- I'm gonna notify the police.
- Leno?
No, no, this is Peter Griffin.
I'm calling to challenge you
to a grudge match
between the Patriots
and the London Silly Nannies.
Well, Griffin, if you want to embarrass
yourself, be my guest.
Good. What do you say, England?
Two weeks from now?
See you there.
- Hello?
- Hey, Brady!
What kind of suit
do you want to be buried in?
You kids are gonna love this.
England has such a rich heritage
of great theater.
Cramsat on the bingum
with the gam gum?
Treaches on the upper
with the trang sang.
Croppers to you, you crang sang lubber.
She rogered the boogley!
All right, now listen up,
you limey bum sniffers.
If we're gonna beat
the New England Patriots next week,
I got to toughen you up.
So you're gonna get in shape
the way American athletes do,
by taking steroids.
I say, Jenkins, you give me
that dirty look one more time,
and I've a good mind to get into my PJ's
and have a pillow fight with you.
Very well, then. En garde!
- I like your gown.
- I like yours.
When's the beating gonna come, Brian?
Just tell me when it's gonna come!
Just do something, anything!
Look, look, I'll do it. I'll do it first.
Look, I'll do it even worse.
Look how hurt I am.
We're even now!
- You're going down, Brady!
- You're the one who's going down, Griffin!
What the hell?
- Those men are tremendous in stature.
- And they're coming straight at us!
Oh!
We'll take my carriage.
Oh, crap!
Well, I'm still here, you bastards,
so let's do this.
Hey, Brady, you're gonna gloat
and call me a loser now?
Actually, Peter, you're not a loser at all.
- What you did just now was pretty ballsy.
- Really?
Absolutely! For one guy
to stand up
to the entire New England Patriots team.
That's a winner in my book.
Wow. Thanks, Tom Brady.
- Peter! Oh, my God, are you all right?
- Yeah.
- Can you move your legs?
- Yeah!
Oh, good.
I thought you were gonna be a vegetable,
and I gotta tell you, Peter,
I just don't think I have it in me.
I mean, if you can't move, it's over.
I love you, too, honey. Let's go home.
Thank you for watching «Family Guy» on
www.FOX-fan.ru